Hi to this new video I'm in my bedroom
4chains and I thought about this video
really hard because this is the five
most extraordinary things from my
wardrobe and I laid them down here all
around me I really had to think hard
because I own a lot of stuff to be honest and a lot of cool stuff a lot of
unusual stuff but I think I narrowed it down to these five and I hope you're
going to enjoy them all right let's start with a special dress it's really
heavy and you may have guessed it it's made of datex lytics on the outside
fabric on the inside. Now come on.
It's a floor-long dress and the unusual thing is that there is a spray painting
at the front and at the back. So they basically just went ahead and sprayed
this motif here. The original artwork is from a German tattoo artist. I'll link
him in the description box. This is super heavy because it's a lot of fabric right
at the end here and it makes a great silhouette but see for yourself.
This dress is from Ledapol and I think it's totally unique with the printing going on.
Sadly you can see that the paint is going to rub off over time but I'll try
to keep it nice as long as it's possible. It's super comfortable because of the
day-tax material so super easy to put on and it just feels like a fabric from the
inside although I still think that it's kind of heavy I went partying with it
evening in Munich and people asked me about it a lot because it is really
unique next up is a really cool jacket from
Schnittmuskel a German label and the special thing about this one is the back
and that it is 100% handmade. So when I said to the designer I want to have such
a jacket she sat down and sewed everything on herself. So every jacket is
one-of-a-kind and really unique.
So you have to imagine the work that goes in such a jacket.
And I really like all the ribbons here and the elastics.
And also there is really cut out here at the side.
I think this is a super great everyday item but with a lot of style.
Alright and for the next item I have to take down my bedroom decoration
because I normally keep it like a painting on my wall.
It's covered in dust on the inside because this year without all the festivals and parties
I did not have that much occasions to wear it.
So this is made by AMF corsets.
hand painted and I love this design I acquired it when I went shopping quite
tipsy at the wave graphic treffin I think two years ago and then some weeks
later I drove to Berlin to pick this up because Louis Fleishauer made it for me
so so far all the things I showed you are really totally unique pieces and I
that's quite fitting for this video the corset is made of leather and I said to
him I want an over bust one I want these rips here and I want this design it's
called frozen and for the next item I have to change completely and I'll need
these any idea all right this is a latex catsuit and it is matte latex and some
shiny latex and fake big boobs and this one was a show outfit from German
Fertigsprache last year it is made by shiitake follow the mushroom latex couture
whatever he's calling himself at the moment. And I love this one because it is so much
going on here. A lot of details. These buckles and the integrated belts and
this textured latex here and at the leg again. The original outfit had attached
shoe covers fitting to this design and from this show there is a video which I'm
going to show you now
I'll keep wearing this one for the moment because it's always a lot of effort to get
into it.
And I'm moving on to the last item.
I waited with this one until the end because my makeup is going to be ruined
after I put this on. It is a cute bunny mask
by Jean Jouel and I already took some pictures with this one which I can show you
this one's pretty cute with the floppy ear here I think I have to come up with some new occasions
to wear this one because I have not worn this one as often as I would like to but
nevertheless I think this is pretty cool and normally it is in my living room on
top of a cupboard so it's another piece of decoration for my home and with that
I say goodbye going to eat that carrot now and I hope you're having a good time
see ya
Thank you.